Hmm. It's kind of like
the Loch Ness monster.
(Leonard:)Maybe there's something there,
maybe there isn't. We'll never know.
(Leonard:)But sometimes it's fun to creep
yourseIf out thinking about it.
(Mrs Cooper:)How are you doing
on the young Lady front?
(Mrs Cooper:)I hear you're in some sort
of a long-distance situation?
(Leonard:)Uh. Yeah, it's Raj's sister.
It's kind of tough. She's in lndia.
(Leonard:)Her parents aren't happy
she's dating someone white.
(Mrs Cooper:)Oh, that's a funny turn, isn't it?
Because you... You never think about it
going the other way.
(Mrs Cooper:)Well, you can't force things.
(Mrs Cooper:)Figure out if you're in a relationship or if
you're just calling it one. Like they say:
"A cat can have kittens in the oven,
but that don't make them biscuits."
That reminds me of another saying:
"You can lead a chicken to Crisco,
but you can't make your mother fry it."
(Mrs Cooper:)You pester me one more time
about chicken...